[{"answer": "Well, let's call her up. What can we lose", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Well, what do you feel like doing tonight", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I didn't like her, my friend. I don't feel like calling her up", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't know. What do you feel like doing", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah, sure", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You call her up for yourself, my friend. I don't feel like calling her up", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh, he'll get married, don't worry, Aunt my friend", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well, there's the Stardust Ballroom. That's a kind of a big dance hall. Every Saturday night, it's just loaded with girls. It's a nice place to go. You pay sevent", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend, I don't want you hang arounna house tonight. I want you to go take a shave and go out and dance", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You gonna get married", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Ma, I'm gonna stay home and watch my friend", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "So I'll die without a son", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Blue suit, gray suit, I'm still a fat man. A fat ugly man", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " I'm ugly... I'm ugly! I'm UGLY", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I'm just gonna get my cigarettes. I left them in my coat", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'll see you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I gotta pain in my left side, and my leg throbs like a drum", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I gotta pains in my shoulder too. I have a pain in my hip, and my right arm aches so much I can't sleep. It's a curse to be old. How you feel", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't think I remember him", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I wake up this morning, I hear the baby crying. So I wake up. I come in their room. That girl is shaking her hand atta baby. I said,", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "That's my son my friend's baby", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "So there you are. So I guess I'm not such a dog as I think I am", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't know either. I think I'm a very nice guy. I also think I'm a pretty smart guy in my own way", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You gotta Ladies' Room around here", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " my friend back", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm afraid of being lonely", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Actually, I don't make friends easily", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know the people, of course, but as a rule, I don't think a mothe", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I don't think a mother should depend so much upon her children for her rewards in life", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend, gimme a coupla minutes, because I promised Mr. my friend I'd let him know tomorrow. See, what I wanna know, my friend, if a buncha individual retail merchants get together, how does it operate? On individual mar", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No, I don't know. That's why I'm asking you", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Who", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Your son my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Don't bring her to the house no more", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I don't know! She don't look like Italian to me. Plenny a nice Italian girls around", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " I don't feel like playing cards. Waddaya feel like doing tonight, my friend", "docId": "Marty.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " I don't know, my friend. my friend you feel like doing", "qsentId": 38}]